Slow down, slow down,
go back, go back, fine.
Be careful sir!
Be careful!
Were they your parents?
May God bless their soul.
That's fine.
It's a two-storey grave, right?
Move it a bit.
A bit more.
Go to the car, I'm coming.
- Let me fix this.
- Go get the other one.
That's ok sir.
Good for them.
They sleep alongside each
other even in the other world.
I didn't even have such luck in this world.
We are good now, sir. Thanks.
I meant no offence, Madam.
There's one more left.
That's fine, leave it. I'll set it myself.
It's really heavy!
Here you are.
I heard you are moving to a new house.
I thought, if you needed...
No need, That's for you,
please take it... Take it.
Madam, we agreed on 50,
but this is only 40.
The missing 10 is to teach you not
to talk too much while working.
When I Became A Butterfly
Freely based on a true story
Rascal
Bastard
Evill
Slacker
That's how you call those who
don't care about their honor.
Miserable.
Recently Hamid told me this once. But
I didn't know the meaning.
Stupid as he is, He probably
dosen't know its meaning either.
Why is the door left open?
It's geting cold in here.
Instead, but it gets warm up here.
Kasra, Kasra, could you bring
me the laundry detergent?
I'm busy now.
Aren't you going to fix the washing machine?
It's been out of order for 3 months.
I need to call a repariman
to come and fix it.
Then give him a call!
Let me find one of my
friend who does this job.
Of course, you are not the one
washing the clothes by hand.
You have been ruining my life for 3 months.
Lately you've become interested
in late-night movies!
Mr. Mostafa's spouse, it's your turn.
Mr.Mostafa's spouse... Mr.Mostafa's spouse.
Yes, Hello.
Hello, please tell Mr. Mostafa
not to throw his cigarette butts down here.
It's been a few days I wanted to
tell him, but he didn't show up.
I didn't want to bother you and
knock on your door to tell you this.
I'm sorry! I will tell him.
You keep saying "I'm sorry" all the time.
Yesterday, he threw a cigarette butt it
was about to fall in my customer's collar.
I was the one who got embarrassed, not him.
He doesn't care at all.
I said that I'm sorry, I'll tell him.
You guys have a great patio, why doesn't
he go there to smoke his cigarettes?
Why does he have to smoke by the window?
Where's Kasra?
I sent him to buy cigarettes for me.
Why didn't you ask me to buy them for you?
It's not appropriate for a lady!
Do you think it is appropriate for a kid?
What that nosy jerk was saying again?
Thanks God he can only exert his power on birds.
Otherwise, he would also put humans in cage.
You bought fish again? I
can't stand its gross smell!
It can't be worse than
the smell of cigarettes.
What?
It can't be worse than
the smell of cigarettes.
How can you tolerate the fish
smell but not my cigarette smell?
How about you? You can put up with the
gross cigarettes smell but not fish?
Clean it up! You aren't scared
of its dead body, are you?
I am not scared, I just find it disgusting.
Give me a break! You find me disgusting too,
but why don't you shout when you see me?
Don't start again.
In front of the kid, you ask me not to argue.
In his absence, you also ask me not to argue.
So when can I share with you
the stuff I have on my heart?
Whenever I die, come to my grave
and talk freely.
- Then, I wouldn't argue with you.
- Really?
Listen, when I die, you have no right
to visit me and say even one word.
Because, I've heard more than
enough of you in this world.
Dad, can you pass me the water?
Take it yourself my friend. Is it too hard?
Because in our book, it is mentioned:"
Dad gives water, Dad gives the bread".
Nothing is mentioned about what mom gives?
Be careful, wait.
Make sure it doesn't scratch the wall.
I swear. I can't stand him anymore.
For sure, he says he has quit his
addiction, it has been a month now.
But he takes it as an excuse
to sit at home all the time.
Neither he looks for a job, nor
even steps out of the house.
How come it is none of your business?
You are his mother!
Tell him something, for God's sake, He might listen
to you more than me, what I say, he does against it.
No, no problem. I am sorry I
called during the call for prayer.
Please pray for me.
Allo! What the hell, you called so early?
Now that you woke me up, you can
keep saying your nonsense words.
Where are you?
See you in 10 minutes by the lamp-post.
You have a cellphone, why do you give
the landline number to your friends?
- My cellphone is turned off.
- Then turn it on!
You can't just pass the
landline number to everybody.
For God's sake, go back to sleep! You think
I'm eager to listen to your repetitive words?
I was asleep! The call woke me up!
Kasra!
Get up son! Get up!
Get up, I need your help.
Good morning.
It's a secret between us, don't
tell mum about it. Alright?
What do you have in your hand? Huh?
I said what do you have in your hand?
Give me your hand!
What do you have in your hand? Huh?
What do you have in your hand?
- Daddy!
- What did you give to the kid?
Mind your own business! Do I ever meddle
in your cooking and vacuum cleaning?
Aren't you ashamed?
Didn't you swear never to touch drugs again?
Now you want to get your kid involved in this?
Get out of here, wife.
That nosy jerk down there has reported
me to the police thousands of times.
If I step out, they'll catch me.
Unless you want this?
Why should the police arrest you? Huh? Why?
Get out of here. You are
getting on my nerves!
Look, I swear I won't let
the kid to go out! I swear!
Daddy! My hand! Ouch!
If you can take it out of his
hand, I'll give you a medal.
Ouch! My hand.
- Give it to me! - I won't.
- You are really setting me off!
Kasra will need to walk over my
dead body before walking out.
Do you want the neighbors to hear us?
I don't care, it's not
like it's the first time.
Then give me the damn thing!
I won't! You call yourself a man?
Does a man do such things to his kids?
I'm not a kid!
Does a man earn money like this?
What's wrong with it?
You know very well how to spend the money.
If you don't want to work, I'll work like a man to
avoid begging from you and your dirty business.
I can't work? Do you remember the
job I had in this slaughterhouse.
You were complaining so much about
the smell that I had to leave it.
Of course! They kicked you out like a dog
when they found out you were a drug addict!
Give it to me. They didn't kick me
out, they were all junkies out there.
- Go do your duty properly if you can!
- That duty, huh?
Give me that shit! Give it to me!
Give it to me!
Daddy?
Daddy! Are you ok?
Daddy, wake up! Open your eyes!
Daddy, get up, daddy!
Get up! Are you ok? For God's sake...
Get up. Dad!
Open the door! I want to get out.
For God's sake open the door!
Mum open the door, I want to get out.
Why do you want to get out?
Open it! Open the door.
Do you promise not to make any noise?
I promise.
Do you promise not to escape?
You killed him?
Me?
Was it my fault?
Yes, it was your fault.
I want my dad, you killed him.
I'm no match for your dad, I'm weak.
He fell himself.
No, you killed him.
He started the fight and pulled my scarf.
It was his fault.
Do you know what is the penalty of
drug deal? You were going to do this
Do you know what the police
will do if they understand?
It didn't matter to your
father, but it did to me.
I want my dad.
Here, if you think I am guilty, call
the police so they arrest me now.
They will take me to prison
and you to an orphanage.
Where's dad?
In the yard.
I want my dad.
We can't keep him here. We need
to take him out of the house.
From now on, only use
the toilets in the yard.
Kasra? Kasra?
Won't you give me a hand?
Kasra?
Leave me alone! Crazy,
murderer, miserable, killer.
Let me go! I want to tell everyone.
Open the door! Open the door!
I've prepared your breakfast.
It's on the table.
I'm going out, do you need anything?
Don't touch daddy until I return
and see what we can do, ok?
Ok?
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
Of a dead body?
It's not scary, It's like a toy or a doll.
I know, but still.
You claim to have become a man.
And now you're scared of a dead body?
It is Dad.
It was dad! It's only a corpse, now. From
now on I'm both your mom and dad, got it?
And you are both my son
and the man in this house.
You too are scared.
I used to be afraid when
he was alive, not now.
I need you now. If you want to prove me
you've become a man, now it's the time.
Being a man isn't about the things
your dad used to tell you about.
It's about being brave and afraid of
nothing. Its about not crying. Ok?
I didn't want this to happen.
But it did happen.
Hi! Thanks a lot.
If I knew he would listen you so
well, I would've told you earlier.
Believe me I told him several
times, he wouldn't listen to me.
Send him my regards.
I haven't seen him lately!
Shall I make it 1 kilo?
No, half a kilo is enough.
Look, it's a first-class lamb meat. It
will be sold out by the time you come back.
It's ok, thanks.
How's Mr. Mostafa?
Has he found a job?
Not yet.
I told him several times not
to leave the slaughterhouse.
But he wouldn't listen, he assumed
he could get another job easily.
- Hi!
- Hi! How are you?
Fine. Mr. Kamal, Mostafa is
asking for a favor tonight.
Sure, what is it about?
We want to sell some old furniture.
What kind of furniture?
A dresser and other stuff like that.
Can I see them? Are they
still in a good condition?
- Yes, actually they're sold, sorry.
- What time shall I come?
Come around sunset.
Park the van by the door.
We will load the van ourself and let
you know when we are done.
Tell me if I can help.
Thanks, we'll load them ourself
as they're quite fragile.
Are you sure?
Yes, thanks.
Ok, where are you sending them to?
We will give you the address tonight.
At your service.
Just send my regards to Mr.Mostafa
and tell him to treat me more fairly.
Hello, is Mr. Mostafa at home?
No, he isn't.
We had an appointment two days ago.
He didn't show up and hasn't
answered his phone since.
- I'm worried about him, is he ok?
- Yes, but he isn't home.
If he is at home, please tell him Faramarz is
waiting outside and urgently needs to see you.
I told you he's not at home.
Don't come here anymore.
I have no one in the
neighborhood except Mr.Mostafa.
Please don't disturb us anymore.
I don't mean to disturb anybody!
I am just begging you to tell him
to turn on his cellphone. Bye!
Tell him I won't come here anymore.
I was just worried about him. Bye!
It was grandma, she
wanted to talk to dad.
I said he's in the shower.
She said she would come tomorrow.
- Yes?
- Hi! I brought you the car, shall I park it by the door?
Hello Mr. Kamal, we've cancelled
moving the furniture tonight.
Mostafa was supposed to tell you,
but it seems he forgot to do it.
No problem, is he at home now?
Yes, he says hi.
Can you tell him to come out a second? I need to
see him briefly. I couldn't see him for ages!
He is busy right now, he can't.
No problem, I'll be waiting
outside until his job is done.
He said he will be busy for a
while, what do you want from him?
Tell him sorry, please give back the
40 thousand tomans borrowed last month.
I need it to repair the car, otherwise
I swear I wouldn't even mention it.
Hi, I'm really sorry I'm bothering
you, but it is Mostafa's fault.
He told me just for one day but it's been a month
now, otherwise I wouldn't bother you for it.
Please send my regards to him.
Hi, tell Mostafa to come here.
He isn't home.
He was there a minute ago.
Well now he is not here anymore,
what do you want from him?
Don't you know who I am
and what I want? Huh?
I'll tel him to call you
as soon as he comes back.
Stop it! Tell him to come
here, I know he's there!
I told you he's not here, go away!
Look! Tell him a man doesn't hide himself
in his house and send his wife out!
A man doesn't beg for 250
grams of drug and disappears.
And what do you want me to do about it?
I want you to go inside now and ask him how
many days does he want to hide himself there?
At the end I'll get him whenever he
is out and I'll get my money back.
I'll call the police if
you don't leave right away.
The police? Call them to capture the
thing, if it is going to be taken up.
One more word and I will tell
him you've been bothering me!
Look, tell him if he believes that he
can get away with it, he's dead wrong.
Tell him to turn on his phone, now!
I can't stay here anymore, mom.
Neither can I, but I have to.
Until when you want to keep daddy?
Until he wants.
But he's dead,
He does not understand anything.
He didn't understand when he was alive too.
But I knew what he wanted.
I really miss him.
Do you want to give him a massage?
He used to like it very much.
Why did you come upstairs
with your foot ache?
Let me wake him up to come downstairs.
No, don't do that if he is
tired, don't wake him up.
He didn't sleep the whole night,
you know he's been in rehab these days.
But he gets upset if I don't wake him up.
No problem.
When he gets up, he will come downstairs.
Whenever he decides to quit his addiction, he
sleeps from morning to night to control his stress.
Try to be more lenient with him.
Life is shorter than this which a lady argues
with her husband, God doesn't like it.
What kind of argument? We
are good with each other.
But it seems you are always nagging at him.
It's not true, It is so common
among each and every couple.
If I tell you some things,
I just open up my heart to you.
And I am here to do the same.
My girl, I am old enough, my death is
near, I have pain in my whole body.
But I can still think.
We, old women, when our husband were talking to us, we couldn't
keep our chin up even if they hit us, we were more tolerate.
Because of that, marriages
were ever-lasting.
What if more matrimonial stuff were taught at universities and other
organizations, It would be more useful than anything else for women.
Thanks God that I don't go none of those places! By the way, Mostafa
found a job, he is going to go south with one of his friend.
Ok, Thanks God,
be thankful to God.
Yes, everything is going to be better.
He is overcoming his addiction as
well as finding a job, Thanks God.
Kasra you sweetheart, check
TV, when is praying time?
Kasra? Don't you need anything?
Aren't you hungry?
Kasra?
I don't wanna hear you crying anymore.
Understood? even one more time.
Give me a pocket of that cigarette please.
What kind of?
The red one.
This one?
No, that one.
Here you are.
Give two.
Sorry, three.
Take it, it is not female.
Let the clutch in tightly, shift the gear then
let the clutch out slowly and give it some gas.
If you let the clutch suddenly
out, this happens again.
Shift the gear!
Clutch!
Becareful!
Brake now!
I really wanted to kick his ass!
Eh!?
What did I say?!
Of being a man, why you've
learned impoliteness?
It's out of my control, I do my best to
forget those words but I can't be successful.
I have a good memory.
A good memory forgets bad stuff.
- Hello.
So, where is it?
There.
What's wrong with it?
It's working, but the water
is leaking from all its parts.
All its part?
Mainly lower section.
Lower.
Its tubs, its belt is out of order I guess.
I will take a look at it.
What a lovely smell "Espand".
I'm really crazy about such smell.
Here you are.
Wow, what a vivid tea, Thanks a lot.
Whenever, I don't drink tea, I
become like a car without fuel.
This tea can be taken
as a premium gas for me.
Is it clear how much does it cost?
Be my guest.
Just give me a discount.
Sure, I told you be my guest.
I imagine that I got stuck in the traffic.
No way.
Yeah, why not?
You know what, I am not
used to talk while working.
Let me finish this, and then
we will discuss about it.
Excuse me.
Well, It's done lady.
How soon!
Don't put it on uneven ground.
You were lucky that water
didn't go into the engine.
I changed its rubber, hose and belt.
In total, 27 thousand.
There's no God just one.
Well done!
Turn!
Let's go daddy.
Mr. Mostafa!
Mr. Mostafa! I wanted to
talk to you for a second.
Who the hell is he.
- Hello.
- I came for the job ad!
- Yes, go to our manager.
- Hello.
I came for recruitment.
Thanks, I recruited one.
- Hen or rooster?
- Rooster.
Because we can use its eggs.
Rooster can only make some noises.
In the name of God.
Cut it in pieces?
No, just remove its feathers.
Tell Mr. Mostafa that it is unfaithful to
act like that behaviour two nights ago.
Take me with you too.
No it's not needed.
Mostafa, Mr Mostafa... Mostafa.
Mr. Mostafa.
What the hell did you do, sir?
Are you blind?
You men are always
criticizing women's driving,
I'm talking to you, are you dumb?
Where?
You damaged my car, now you leaving, sir?
Hello, How are you?
Because, Mostafa called you two, three
times when he was going to south.
But you didn't answer, we became worried.
I don't know, maybe you
were saying your prayer.
Yes he went.
He was in hurry.
He said he would call you
when he arrives there.
I don't know, he went with one
of his friend whom I didn't know.
A friend in his military service.
He said he is going to work and save
money to solve all of our problems.
Hope in God.
Thanks, bye.
- Hi!
What I can do for you?
I came for recruitment.
Last name?
Kaviani.
First name?
Parvaneh.
How old are you?
I was born in 1982
Married or Single?
Married with one son.
You Kidding!
What's his name?
Kasra.
Kasra with A at the end?
Yes.
Do you have any experience in sales?
Yes, sure. For a couple of years.
I love sales, some of our customers
used to get there just for me.
Great!
I don't know, every time I called
him, his cell phone is off.
I got butterflies in my stomach.
I called every where!
Police stations, hospital,
forensic medicine.
I don't know even what city he went to.
Excuse me, I made you worried.
Generally, he is a happy-go-lucky person,
perhaps he has lost his cellphone.
He is not even thinking about calling us.
No, why you! With your foot ache.
I will look for him.
Yes, pray for him that
nothing happens for him.
Ok, sure.
Thanks, bye.
Follow me please.
These are our coat set.
All of them are made overseas.
This one is rich velvet.
This one is corduroy.
And the last one is plaid wool
one in two available colors.
This one in 5
and that one in 3 colors
Tell me which one do you prefer to try it
on and see whether it looks good on you.
For what occasion do you want to wear?
Hi! I am Kasra.
Kasra.
- Hi!
- Hi! My son.
How early you came!
Dad told "I would be home in one hour"
let's go sooner, ok.
You look so pretty, mom!
I'm always pretty!
Let's go home with your
current appearance, ok?
No way!
The neighbors might see us.
No problem, who cares?
You want our neighbors label
me in your dad's absence?
Mom! Why don't we have a car?
Didn't you ask your dad?
Yup, he said at least we have a motorcycle.
But you are a lady, motorcycle
is not appropriate for you.
You should have a car.
One's value is not
measured by his shortage.
So how?
It's about the things he desires to have.
Mom!
Are we miserable?
No...
Neither miserable nor fortunate.
You know who is miserable?
The one who has learned to tolerate misery.
I don't know what to say.
She's coming.
His friend called in the morning with an
unknown Number. I guess somewhere from South.
I am not sure where he was calling from.
He told they went for drug dealing.
I don't know what happend.
Police got there, there was shooting
and then Mostafa and his friend escaped.
I wish I was dead! why did you let
him continue his dirty business again?
Me?
I did insist on keeping him away from
these stuff. He lied to me as well.
Now where is he?
Is he ok?
I don't know, his friend
didn't know where he is.
He told Mostafa is escapee.
He was shot.
My God!
He doesn't stop doing
this until he kills me.
If I hadn't listend to dad, you
wouldn't have argued with him...
And now he would be alive.
If I hadn't caught a cold 11 years ago...
I would never have gone to drug
store to see your dad there.
And now I wouldn't have had you at all.
If he wasn't stronger than you...
He wouldn't pull the scarf off your hand
and he wouldn't fall down the steps.
You know how much you kicked
my womb to see this world?
Can I count on you till the end?
I can't stand staying in this home, this
neighborhood, not even this people anymore.
I don't know how I tolerated this month.
Since everybody has understand what the hell
Mostafa did, they look at me in different way.
Their look makes me sick.
Do you know what I found
in the basement last night?
His cellphone!
He hid it in the basement.
I really don't know what he was thinking, he
didn't want anybody's call until he was back.
Kasra is suffering too.
Nor I want Neither can he go to
school in this neighborhood.
With your permission,
I decided to sell the house.
I want to go to a place where
nobody knows me and Kasra.